<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Our Recipies</title><link>https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/</link><description>Recent content on Our Recipies</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 01:45:53 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cider Pie</title><link>https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/cider-pie/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 01:45:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/cider-pie/</guid><description>Ingredients 5-6 medium sized granny smith apples 4 tsp cinnamon 1 cup cider syrup 1/2 cup sugar 1/2 cub maple syrup 8 tbsp butter 1 tbsp vanilla 4 eggs 1 pie crust 1 Directions Solid fillings Peel apples, and cut into small pieces. In a large pan, saute apples with 4 tbsp butter and connamon until soft Set aside once done. Liquid fillings In a medium sauce pan, combine 1/2 cup sugar, 1/2 cup maple syrup, 1 cup cider syrup, and 4 tbsp butter.</description></item><item><title>Cider Syrup</title><link>https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/cider-syrup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 01:38:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/cider-syrup/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 gallon of apple cider Directions Place cider into large, flatbottomed pot Bring cider to a boil Reduce heat to a simmer. Let simmer until volume has reduced to 2 1/3 cup (A 7:1 reduction). Make sure to scrape the sides of the pot while reducing Syrup will become much more viscous as it reduces. Target viscosity will leave a notable trail in the pot when the bottom is wiped with a spatula.</description></item><item><title>Cider Jammy Dodgers</title><link>https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/cider-jammy-dodgers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 01:29:54 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/cider-jammy-dodgers/</guid><description>Ingredients 8 ounces (227 grams) butter unsalted, softened 2/3 cup (64 grams) granulated sugar 2 large eggs, room temperature 1 teaspoon vanilla extract 2 1/4 cups (330 grams) all-purpose flour 1/4 teaspoon salt 1/2 cup (64 grams) cider syrup Directions Combine butter, sugar and eggs.
Add the butter (227g) and sugar (64g) to a stand mixer or mixing bowl. Beat until light and fluffy. Add the eggs and continue to mix.</description></item><item><title>Dry Fry Chicken</title><link>https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/dry-fry-chicken/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 01:29:54 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/dry-fry-chicken/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 celery stalks, outer stems peeled 1 pound boneless chicken, chopped into 1-inch chunks 3 scallions, ends trimmed 1/4 cup peanut oil 8 dried hot red chiles (preferably Sichuan chiles) 1 teaspoon whole Sichuan peppercorns 1 1/2 tablespoons chili bean paste 1 tablespoon Shaoxing rice wine or medium-dry sherry 1 teaspoon dark soy sauce Salt 2 teaspoons sesame oil Directions Slice celery at steep angle into ½-inch slices. Set aside and toss with pinch of salt.</description></item><item><title>Beans and Rice</title><link>https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/beans-and-rice/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:54:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://cookbook.greenstuff.io/beans-and-rice/</guid><description>Ingredients Kidney beans black beans potatoes onion powder garlic powder salt pepper rice cumin cinnamon vegetable out Directions Acquire kidney beans, black beans, potatoes, garlic powder, onion powder, salt, black pepper, cooking oil, rice, and optionally cumin and cinnamon. Add one half part kidney beans, one half part black beans, and four parts water into a large pot. Bring the water to a strong boil, and then stir, and reduce to a simmer.</description></item></channel></rss>